Y'all, we're here for another episode of Small Doses Podcast, and I am joined by
Saira Rao, Rao, Rao, Rao. Y'all, we're here for another episode of Small Doses Podcast,
and I am joined by Saira Rao and Regina Jackson. These two fierce warriors of patience, okay,
and knowledge, put tables together of Karens and deconstructed them. They had to face them
with their racism in their face, and boy, it was quite entertaining to watch. But it was also
necessary, and it continues to be, and they continue to tour and talk about anti-racism,
along with gun control and just the idea of the fact that we need to get smarter because this
world is getting dumber. And they are joining us right here at Small Doses Podcast for side effects
of deconstructing Karen. I want you to drop your questions in the comments for these two fierce
leaders, and I want us to really get to the bottom of, can we deconstruct the Karen,
or are they here forever? Drop in your comments right here at Small Doses.